RAYMOND SCHONE

508-322-0927 | Plymouth, MA 02360 | ray66928@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Proud Veteran and experienced professional with advanced technical and leadership training. Highly organized and efficient in fast-paced multitasking environments; able to prioritize effectively to accomplish objectives with creativity, enthusiasm, and humor.

Technical Skills

• **Programming Languages**: C, C++, Java HTML/CSS

• Database: SQL, Microsoft Access

• **Networks**: General knowledge of TCP/IP and troubleshooting

• Operating Systems: Mac OS X, UNIX/Linux

• Development Tools: Visual Studio

• **Application**: MS Suite

Professional Experience

Campus Safety Officer/Dispatcher, TeamOps

1/2021-5/2021

- Patrol all areas of Dean College and enforce all Dean College and TeamOps regulations.
- Perform Dispatcher duties of answering phones and updating the Activity Tracker and watching the cameras.

Sales Associate, Bath and Body Works

7/2020-1/2021

- Organizes entire stock room to the management's specifications with all the stock that comes in the shipments daily.
- Consistently execute the selling model and Meets selling goals/expectations during scheduled shifts also, builds highly satisfied and loyal customer base through engagement, conversion and capturing customer phone and e-mail

Work Study Student, Quincy College

9/2019-5/2020

Preformed Helpdesk duties to include answering phones and assisting student with answering
questions to the best of my knowledge. Also was in charge of the student lounge and
troubleshooting computer issues.

Squad Leader, United States Army

7/2008-7/2016

 Placed top 20% in the Army's Basic Leaders Course, Receiving the award for Commandant's list. Conducted monthly job performance, goal setting, and career development counseling. Received instructions from management and delegated work responsibilities to employees. Selected to perform managerial duties in the absence of a supervisor.

Education

Bridgewater State University, Bridgewater, MA

Fall 2020-present

• Bachelors Degree in Computer Science candidate

Summer 2023

Quincy College, Quincy, MA GPA 3.73

• Certificate in Computer Science

Spring 2020